A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices, Mexico, RG 6, SG 13 FA398
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Office Files, 1943-1965; 1
  - O.E.E. - Nutrition Report, 1947-1950 (Box 44, Folder 498)
  - O.E.E. - Office Personnel, 1958-1962 (Box 44, Folder 499)
  - O.E.E. - Parker, Dorothy (O.E.E. Library History), 1954 (Box 44, Folder 500)
  - O.E.E. - Pastures and Forage Crops, 1954-1957 (Box 44, Folder 501)
  - O.E.E. - Plant Physiology, 1943-1955 (Box 44, Folder 502)
  - O.E.E. Potato Improvement - 1953-1955 Poultry Program - 1949-1958 (Box 44, Folder 503)
  - O.E.E. - Program, 1950, 1953-1955 (Box 44, Folder 504)
  - O.E.E. - Program, 1950, 1953-1955 (Box 44, Folder 505)
  - O.E.E. - Program, 1957-1959 (Box 45, Folder 506)
  - O.E.E. - Project #1 - Corn and Sorghum, 1944-1957 (Box 45, Folder 507)
  - O.E.E. - Project #2 - Wheat, 1945-1956 (Box 45, Folder 508)
  - O.E.E. - Project #3 - Beans and Soybeans, 1953-1958 (Box 45, Folder 509)
  - O.E.E. - Project #4 - Vegetables, 1951-1956 (Box 45, Folder 510)
  - O.E.E. - Project #5 - Forage Grasses and Legumes, 1953-1956 (Box 45, Folder 511)
  - O.E.E. - Project #6 - Soil Productivity and Management, 1944-1960 (Box 45, Folder 512)
  - O.E.E. - Project #7 - Insect Pests and Their Control, 1945-1958 (Box 45, Folder 513)
  - O.E.E. - Project #8 - Plant Diseases and Their Control, 1947-1958 (Box 45, Folder 514)
  - O.E.E. - Project #9 - Weeds and Their Control, 1954-1958 (Box 45, Folder 515)
  - O.E.E. - Project #10 - Poultry and Poultry Products, 1954-1956 (Box 45, Folder 516)
  - O.E.E. - Project #11 - Agricultural Information, 1956 (Box 45, Folder 517)
  - O.E.E. Publications - 1953-1956 Radio Programs - 1954-1955 (Box 45, Folder 518)
  - O.E.E. - Reports - Corn, 1954-1958 (Box 45, Folder 519)
  - O.E.E. - Reports - General, 1945-1959 (Box 45, Folder 520)
  - O.E.E. - Reports - Summary, 1943-1944 (Box 45, Folder 521)
  - O.E.E. - Reports - Summary, 1943-1958 (Box 46, Folder 522)
  - O.E.E. - Reports - Summary, 1943-1958 (Box 46, Folder 523)
  - O.E.E. - Reports - Summary, 1943-1958 (Box 46, Folder 524)
  - O.E.E. - Research Activities with Other Official Dependencies, 1954-1957 (Box 46, Folder 525)
  - O.E.E. - Resumes, 1958-1961 (Box 46, Folder 526)
  - O.E.E. - Rice Project, 1956-1960 (Box 46, Folder 527)
  - O.E.E. - Rice Project, 1956-1960 (Box 46, Folder 528)
  - O.E.E. - Seminars, 1948-1960 (Box 46, Folder 529)
  - O.E.E. - Soil Improvement Program, 1946-1958 (Box 46, Folder 530)
  - O.E.E. - Soils Science, 1946-1956 (Box 46, Folder 531)
  - O.E.E. - Sorghums and Soybeans, 1947-1958 (Box 47, Folder 532)
  - O.E.E. - Students (O.E.E. Trainees), 1954-1958 (Box 47, Folder 533)
  - O.E.E. - Technical Personnel, 1944-1960 (Box 47, Folder 534)
  - O.E.E. - Technical Personnel, 1944-1960 (Box 47, Folder 535)
  - O.E.E. - Technical Personnel, 1944-1960 (Box 47, Folder 536)
  - O.E.E. Tillage Practices - 1955-1956 Trainees - 1949-1957 (Box 47, Folder 537)
  - O.E.E. Vegetables Crops - 1952-1956 Vehicles - 1959-1960, 1952-1960 (Box 47, Folder 538)
  - O.E.E. - Weed Control, 1957-1960 (Box 47, Folder 539)
  - O.E.E. - Wheat Improvement Program, 1953-1956 (Box 47, Folder 540)
  - O.E.E. Wheat Increase Program - 1943-1957 Wheat Introductions (Box 47, Folder 541)
  - O.E.E. - Wheat Reports, 1944-1946 (Box 47, Folder 542)
  - O.E.E. - Wheat Reports, 1947-1951, 1958-1960 (Box 48, Folder 543)
  - O.E.E. - Wheat Rust, 1943-1949 (Box 48, Folder 544)
  - O.E.E. - Wheat Varieties, 1943-1944 (Box 48, Folder 545)
  - O.E.E. - Workshops, 1958-1960 (Box 48, Folder 546)
  - Ohio - 1961-1962 Organization of American States - 1960 Orr, Stanley C. - 1962, 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 547)
  - Ortega, Benjamin - 1952-1958 Osler, R.D. - 1958-1959, 1952-1959 (Box 48, Folder 548)
  - Painter, Reginald H., 1960-1962 (Box 48, Folder 549)
  - Panama, 1954-1962 (Box 48, Folder 550)
  - Panama, 1954-1962 (Box 48, Folder 551)
  - Panama, 1954-1962 (Box 48, Folder 552)
  - Pan American Sanitary Bureau, 1948-1949 (Box 48, Folder 553)
  - Papaloapan Watershed - 1952-1953 Paraguay - 1960, 1952-1960 (Box 49, Folder 554)
  - Parker, Dorothy, 1943-1958 (Box 49, Folder 555)
  - Parker, Dorothy, 1943-1958 (Box 49, Folder 556)
  - Patronato para la Investigacion, Fomento y Defensa - Agricola de la Commarca Lagunera, 1952-1956 (Box 49, Folder 557)
  - Pennsylvania - 1960 Peregrina, Rodolfo P. - 1962 Permisos para Importacion/Exportacion de Semilla - 1961, 1960-1962 (Box 49, Folder 558)
  - Perry, Jesse P., 1948-1958 (Box 49, Folder 559)
  - Peru, 1956-1962 (Box 49, Folder 560)
  - Peru, 1956-1962 (Box 49, Folder 561)
  - Peterson, Peter A. - 1959-1960 Philippines - 1959-1962 (Box 49, Folder 562)
  - Phytopathology, 1958-1960 (Box 49, Folder 563)
  - Pino, John A., 1954-1963 (Box 49, Folder 564)
  - Pino, John A., 1954-1963 (Box 49, Folder 565)
  - PL 480 Program, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 566)
  - Plant Pathologists Meeting (Sept. 25-Oct. 6, 1950) - Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 567)
  - Plant Pathologists Meeting - Invitations, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 568)
  - Plant Pathologists Meeting - Invitations, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 569)
  - Plant Pathologists Meeting - Participant Lists, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 570)
  - Plant Pathology, 1952-1959 (Box 50, Folder 571)
  - Point IV Visiting Fellows - 1952-1955 Poland - 1962, 1952-1962 (Box 50, Folder 572)
  - Potato Project - 1955-1960 Poultry Project - 1959, 1955-1959 (Box 50, Folder 573)
  - Press Service (Washington, D.C.) - 1962 Price Waterhouse & Co. - 1961-1962 (Box 50, Folder 574)
  - Productora Nacional de Semillas - 1962 Productos D.D.T., S.A. - 1960, 1960-1962 (Box 50, Folder 575)
  - Programa Cooperative Centroamerican para el Mejoramiento del Maiz, 1961-1963 (Box 50, Folder 576)
  - Project Committee Reports - 1956-1960 Project Ideas - 1956-1959 (Box 50, Folder 577)
  - Project Proposals and Reports, 1956-1960 (Box 50, Folder 578)
  - Proyecto Arquelogico - 1962 Proyectos Constructivos (Oversize Removed) (Box 50, Folder 579)
  - Publications, 1954-1962 (Box 50, Folder 580)
  - Publicity and Technical Publications, 1944-1954 (Box 50, Folder 581)
  - Puebla, State of - 1953-1960 Puerto Rico - 1959-1962, 1953-1962 (Box 50, Folder 582)
  - Purchases, 1959-1963 (Box 51, Folder 583)
  - Purdue Research Foundation - 1958-1960 Purdue University - 1959-1962, 1958-1962 (Box 51, Folder 584)
  - Queretaro, State of - 1950-1959 Quintana Roo, Territory of - 1957-1959 (Box 51, Folder 585)
  - Reports - 1961-1962 Requests for Aid - 1962 (Box 51, Folder 586)
  - Rhodesia, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 587)
  - Richardson, Ralph W., 1951-1962 (Box 51, Folder 588)
  - Richardson, Ralph W., 1951-1962 (Box 51, Folder 589)
  - Rigney, J.A. - 1961-1962 Rinke, E.H. - 1962 (Box 51, Folder 590)
  - Roberts, Lewis M. - 1951-1952 Robinson, H.F. - 1961-1962, 1951-1962 (Box 51, Folder 591)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Directory-Mexico - 1962 Rupert, J.A. - 1946-1952, 1946-1962 (Box 51, Folder 592)
  - Salazar, Angel - 1961 San Luis Potosi, State of - 1954-1961 (Box 52, Folder 593)
  - Scholarships Humanities and Social Sciences (RF) - 1963-1965 Medical and Natural Sciences (RF) - 1965 (Box 52, Folder 594)
  - Scholarships - Non-RF, 1956-1964 (Box 52, Folder 595)
  - Scholarships Scholars and Fellows (RF) - 1958-1965 Scholars and Temporary Trainees (RF) - 1960-1962 (Box 52, Folder 596)
  - Schools - General Correspondence - 1962 Schwarts, Drew - 1960, 1960-1962 (Box 52, Folder 597)
  - Scientific Aides (Non-RF), 1955-1959 (Box 52, Folder 598)
  - Scientific Aides (RF), 1945-1965 (Box 52, Folder 599)
  - Scientific Aides (RF), 1945-1965 (Box 52, Folder 600)
  - Scientific Aides (RF), 1945-1965 (Box 52, Folder 601)
  - Scientific Aides (RF), 1945-1965 (Box 52, Folder 602)
  - Scientific Meetings, 1952-1963 (Box 53, Folder 603)
  - Scientific Meetings, 1952-1963 (Box 53, Folder 604)
  - Scientific Meetings, 1952-1963 (Box 53, Folder 605)
  - Scientific Meetings, 1952-1963 (Box 53, Folder 606)
  - Scientific Meetings - RF Staff Papers, 1952-1955 (Box 53, Folder 607)
  - Scientific Societies, 1955-1962 (Box 53, Folder 608)
  - Scientific Societies, 1955-1962 (Box 53, Folder 609)
  - Scotland, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 610)
  - Secretaria de Agricultura y Fomento - Coop Agricultural Program, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 611)
  - Secretaria de Agricultura y Ganaderia (SAG) - Convenio RF-SAG - Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 612)
  - SAG - Convenio RF_SAG - Original, 1943-1946 (Box 53, Folder 613)
  - SAG - Convenio - Proposed Revisions, 1949, 1953, 1954, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 614)
  - SAG - Convenio - Proposed Revisions, 1949, 1953, 1954, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 615)
  - SAG - Convenio - Proposed Revisions, 1961 (Box 54, Folder 616)
  - SAG - Corn and Sorghum Projects, 1956-1957, 1960 (Box 54, Folder 617)
  - SAG - Extension Meetings, 1954-1955 (Box 54, Folder 618)
  - SAG - Federal Subsidy, 1947-1961 (Box 54, Folder 619)
  - SAG - Federal Subsidy, 1947-1961 (Box 54, Folder 620)
  - SAG - General Correspondence, 1947-1962 (Box 54, Folder 621)
  - SAG - General Correspondence, 1947-1962 (Box 54, Folder 622)
  - SAG - Instituto Nacional de Investigaciones Agricolas (INIA) - Budget, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 623)
  - SAG - Instituto Nacional de Investigaciones Agricolas (INIA) - Budget, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 624)
  - SAG - INIA - General Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 55, Folder 625)
  - SAG - INIA - Inventory and Regulations, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 626)
  - SAG - Listas de Raya - National Research Center at Chapingo, 1945-1948 (Box 55, Folder 627)
  - SAG - Official Mayor (Administrative Officer), 1946-1958 (Box 55, Folder 628)
  - SAG Plan Agricola de Emergencia - 1953-1954 Reports - 1959, 1953-1959 (Box 55, Folder 629)
  - SAG - Seminar Programs (Box 55, Folder 630)
  - SAG - Subsecretary of Agriculture - Jesus Merino Fernandez, 1946-1957 (Box 55, Folder 631)
  - SAG - Subsecretary of Agriculture - Jesus Patino Navarrete, 1959-1962 (Box 55, Folder 632)
  - Secretaria de Economia Nacional - 1947-1958 Secretaria de Educacion Publica - 1948-1955 Secretaria de Gobernacion - 1952-1957, 1947-1957 (Box 55, Folder 633)
  - Secretaria de Hacienda y Credito Publica - 1948 Secretaria de Marina - 1949-1954 Secretaria de Recursos Hidraulicus - 1952-1954 Secretaria de Relaciones Exteriores - 1946-1957 (Box 55, Folder 634)
  - Seed Certification, 1947-1956 (Box 55, Folder 635)
  - Seed Companies, 1959-1962 (Box 55, Folder 636)
  - Seed Laboratory (Chapingo), 1956-1960 (Box 56, Folder 637)
  - Seed Law - 1961 Seed Purchases - 1960, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 638)
  - Seed Requests, 1954-1961 (Box 56, Folder 639)
  - Seed Requests-Shipments, 1959-1962 (Box 56, Folder 640)
  - Seed Requests-Shipments, 1959-1962 (Box 56, Folder 641)
  - Seed Requests-Shipments, 1959-1962 (Box 56, Folder 642)
  - Seed Requests-Shipments, 1959-1962 (Box 56, Folder 643)
  - Seed Requests-Shipments, 1959-1962 (Box 56, Folder 644)
  - Seed Storage, 1957-1961 (Box 56, Folder 645)
  - Sesamum Foundation - 1962 Shank, D.B. - 1959 Simmons, Charles S. - 1961-1962 (Box 57, Folder 646)
  - Sinaloa, State of - 1954-1962 Singleton, Williard R. - 1961-1962 (Box 57, Folder 647)
  - Social Security - 1957 Sociedad Botanica de Mexico - 1961 Sociedad Inter-Americana de Maiz - 1961, 1957-1961 (Box 57, Folder 648)
  - Sociedad Latinoamericana del Maiz - 1961-1962 Sociedad Mexicana de Geografia y Estadistica - 1947 Sociedad Mexicana de Historia Natural - 1960-1961, 1947-1962 (Box 57, Folder 649)
  - Soil Science - Conference, October 1952 (Box 57, Folder 650)
  - Soil Science - Reports, 1946-1959 (Box 57, Folder 651)
  - Solar Cooker, 1956-1961 (Box 57, Folder 652)
  - Solar Cooker, 1956-1961 (Box 57, Folder 653)
  - Sonora, State of - 1952-1962 South Africa - 1961 Southern Corn Improvement Conference - 1960 (Box 57, Folder 654)
  - Soybeans and Sorghums, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 655)
  - Spain - 1958-1962 Special Training Program (Experiment Station Directors) - 1962-1964 (Box 57, Folder 656)
  - Sprague, G.F. - 1959-1962 Spurlock, Richard - 1948-1953, 1948-1962 (Box 57, Folder 657)
  - Stakman, E.C., 1950, 1959-1962 (Box 57, Folder 658)
  - Stanford University - 1959-1960 Statistics on Population and Food Crops - 1962, 1959-1962 (Box 58, Folder 659)
  - Stored Grain Program, 1957-1960 (Box 58, Folder 660)
  - Sugar - 1959-1965 Switzerland - 1962 (Box 58, Folder 661)
  - Tabasco, State of - 1955-1960 Tamaulipas, State of - 1952-1960 Tanganyka - 1959 (Box 58, Folder 662)
  - Taxonomy and Ecology of Native Grasses (R.E. Buller), 1954 (Box 58, Folder 663)
  - Telegrams, 1959-1963 (Box 58, Folder 664)
  - Tennessee - 1959-1960 Tennessee Agricultural and Industrial State University - 1960 Tepalcingo, Mor. - 1960 (Box 58, Folder 665)
  - Texas - 1959-1960 Teziutlan Copper Co. - 1960-1961 Thailand - 1959-1962 (Box 58, Folder 666)
  - Thompson, D.L. - 1962 Timor, East Indies - 1960 Tlaxcala, State of - 1959-1961, 1959-1962 (Box 58, Folder 667)
  - Tractor Maintenance - (n.d.) Travel Grant Applications - 1959 (Box 58, Folder 668)
  - Trinidad - 1959-1962 Tripsacum Collections - 1952 Turk, Kenneth L. - 1958, 1952-1962 (Box 58, Folder 669)
  - Ullstrup, A.J. - 1961-1962 Union Nacional de Productores de Azucar, S.A. de C.V. - 1952-1958, 1952-1962 (Box 58, Folder 670)
  - United States Department of Agriculture - Canning of Orange Juice, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 671)
  - United States Department of Agriculture - General Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 58, Folder 672)
  - United States Department of Agriculture - General Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 59, Folder 673)
  - Universidad de Chihuahua, 1956-1958 (Box 59, Folder 674)
  - Universidad de Sonora, 1957-1961 (Box 59, Folder 675)
  - Universidad Nacional Autonoma Mexicana, 1954, 1959-1962 (Box 59, Folder 676)
  - Uruguay - 1959-1962 Utah State University - 1961 (Box 59, Folder 677)
  - Vallega, Jose - 1961 Vegetable Crops Reports - 1959, 1959-1961 (Box 59, Folder 678)
  - Venezuela - Ensayos Uniformes de Rendimiento Maices, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 679)
  - Venezuela - Eugenio Mendoza Foundation, 1952-1962 (Box 59, Folder 680)
  - Venezuela - General Correspondence, 1956-1962 (Box 59, Folder 681)
  - Venezuela - General Correspondence, 1956-1962 (Box 59, Folder 682)
  - Venezuela Reports - 1952-1954 Universidad Central de Venezuela - 1961-1962, 1952-1962 (Box 59, Folder 683)
  - Veracruz, State of, 1955-1962 (Box 59, Folder 684)
  - Verifax, 1961-1964 (Box 59, Folder 685)
  - Virginia - 1962 Virgin Islands of the United States - 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 686)
  - Visas - 1955-1962 Visiting Scholars (Non-RF) - 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 687)
  - Wallace, H.A. - 1959 Washington, D.C. - 1959-1961 (Box 60, Folder 688)
  - Washington State College, 1941-1951 (Box 60, Folder 689)
  - Weed Control - Reports, 1954-1960 (Box 60, Folder 690)
  - Weed Society of America, 1957-1962 (Box 60, Folder 691)
  - Wellhausen, E.J. - Activity Reports, 1958-1962 (Box 60, Folder 692)
  - Wellhausen, E.J. - General Correspondence, 1951-1962 (Box 60, Folder 693)
  - Wellhausen, E.J. - General Correspondence, 1951-1962 (Box 60, Folder 694)
  - Wellhausen, E.J. - Hybrid Corn Project (Middle East Trip), 1952-1955 (Box 60, Folder 695)
  - Wellhausen, E.J. - Personal, 1958-1962 (Box 60, Folder 696)
  - Wellhausen, E.J. - Reports and Papers, 1953-1960 (Box 61, Folder 697)
  - Wheat Reports, 1954-1960 (Box 61, Folder 698)
  - Wisconsin, 1959-1962 (Box 61, Folder 699)
  - Wortman, L. Sterling - Correspondence and Diaries, 1949-1961 (Box 61, Folder 700)
  - YMCA Rural welfare Program-Comohmila - 1951 Yucatan, State of - 1956-1962 Yugoslavia - 1960-1962, 1951-1962 (Box 61, Folder 701)
  - Zacatecas, State of, 1952-1961 (Box 61, Folder 702)
- Experimental Camp Files, 1943-1965; 2
  - Campo Brisenas, Michoacan, 1945-1946 (Box 62, Folder 703)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Correspondence - Alcala, Roberto Osoyo, 1955-1958 (Box 62, Folder 704)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Correspondence - Duron, Nicholas Sanchez, 1956-1960 (Box 62, Folder 705)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Correspondence - Duron, Nicholas Sanchez, 1956-1960 (Box 62, Folder 706)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Correspondence - General, 1955-1962 (Box 62, Folder 707)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Correspondence - General, 1955-1962 (Box 62, Folder 708)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Correspondence - General, 1955-1962 (Box 62, Folder 709)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Correspondence - Yepez, Samuel Aguilar, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 710)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Expenditures, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 711)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Irrigation and Drainage, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 712)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 713)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 714)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 715)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 716)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 717)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 718)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 63, Folder 719)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. - Reports, 1957 (Box 64, Folder 720)
  - Campo C.I.A.N.O. Sesame Tests - n.d. Water Tanks - 1956-1957 (Box 64, Folder 721)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Budget, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 722)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - Calderon, Jose Guevara, 1957-1958 (Box 64, Folder 723)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - Comite Directivo, 1959 (Box 64, Folder 724)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - General, 1954-1962 (Box 64, Folder 725)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - General, 1954-1962 (Box 64, Folder 726)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - General, 1954-1962 (Box 64, Folder 727)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - General, 1954-1962 (Box 64, Folder 728)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - General, 1954-1962 (Box 64, Folder 729)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - Jasso, Carlos Tapia, 1959-1960 (Box 65, Folder 730)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - Roderiguez, Neftali Bautista, 1953-1959 (Box 65, Folder 731)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - Roderiguez, Neftali Bautista, 1953-1959 (Box 65, Folder 732)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - Roderiguez, Neftali Bautista, 1953-1959 (Box 65, Folder 733)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Correspondence - Sanchez, Leobardo Jimenez, 1960 (Box 65, Folder 734)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Drainage, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 735)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Electrical System, 1956-1957 (Box 65, Folder 736)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Listas de Raya, 1959-May 1960 (Box 65, Folder 737)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Listas de Raya, 1959-May 1960 (Box 65, Folder 738)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Listas de Raya, 1959-May 1960 (Box 65, Folder 739)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Listas de Raya, June 1960-February 1961 (Box 66, Folder 740)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Listas de Raya, June 1960-February 1961 (Box 66, Folder 741)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Maize Production, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 742)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Plant Inventory, 1956 (Box 66, Folder 743)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Progress Report, 1955 (Box 66, Folder 744)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Reports, 1955-1961 (Box 66, Folder 745)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Reports, 1955-1961 (Box 66, Folder 746)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Reports, 1955-1961 (Box 66, Folder 747)
  - Campo Cotaxtla - Sub-projects, 1955-1958 (Box 66, Folder 748)
  - Campo El Cayal - Correspondence - General, 1955-1956 (Box 66, Folder 749)
  - Campo El Cayal - Correspondence - General, 1957-1961 (Box 67, Folder 750)
  - Campo El Cayal - Correspondence - General, 1957-1961 (Box 67, Folder 751)
  - Campo El Cayal - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 67, Folder 752)
  - Campo El Cayal - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 67, Folder 753)
  - Campo El Cayal - Reports, 1955-1958 (Box 67, Folder 754)
  - Campo El Cayal - Sub-projects, 1956-1957 (Box 67, Folder 755)
  - Campo El Cayal - Construction Contracts, 1944-1947 (Box 67, Folder 756)
  - Campo El Cayal - Correspondence - General, 1944-1959 (Box 67, Folder 757)
  - Campo El Cayal - Correspondence - General, 1944-1959 (Box 67, Folder 758)
  - Campo El Cayal - Correspondence - General, 1944-1959 (Box 67, Folder 759)
  - Campo El Horno - Correspondence - General, 1960-1962 (Box 68, Folder 760)
  - Campo El Horno - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 68, Folder 761)
  - Campo El Horno - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 68, Folder 762)
  - Campo El Horno - Plantings, 1953, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 763)
  - Campo El Horno - Projects, 1956-1957 (Box 68, Folder 764)
  - Campo El Horno - Reports, 1956-1957, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 765)
  - Campo El Palmar, 1961-1962 (Box 68, Folder 766)
  - Campo El Progresso, 1946-1949 (Box 68, Folder 767)
  - Campo El Roque - Correspondence - General, 1959-1962 (Box 68, Folder 768)
  - Campo El Roque - Listas de Raya, 1960-1961 (Box 68, Folder 769)
  - Campo El Yaqui, 1946-1948 (Box 68, Folder 770)
  - Campo La Cal Grande - Correspondence - General, 1951-1957 (Box 68, Folder 771)
  - Campo La Cal Grande - Correspondence - General, 1951-1957 (Box 68, Folder 772)
  - Campo La Cal Grande - Correspondence - General, 1958-1961 (Box 69, Folder 773)
  - Campo La Cal Grande - Correspondence - Labor Problems, 1957-1958 (Box 69, Folder 774)
  - Campo La Cal Grande - Correspondence - Land Transfers, 1951-1956 (Box 69, Folder 775)
  - Campo La Cal Grande - Drainage, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 776)
  - Campo La Cal Grande - Listas de Raya, 1959-1961 (Box 69, Folder 777)
  - Campo La Cal Grande - Meteorological Data, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 778)
  - Campo La Cal Grande - Projects, 1955-1957 (Box 69, Folder 779)
  - Campo La Cal Grande Topographical Data - 1953 Water Analysis - 1957 (Box 69, Folder 780)
  - Campo La Campana - Correspondence - General, 1957-1962 (Box 69, Folder 781)
  - Campo La Campana - Correspondence - General, 1957-1962 (Box 69, Folder 782)
  - Campo La Campana Expenditures - 1957-1959 Listas de Raya - 1960-1961 (Box 69, Folder 783)
  - Campo Leon, 1943-1950 (Box 69, Folder 784)
  - Campo Pabellon - 1945-1946 Campo Queretaro - 1945-1946 (Box 69, Folder 785)
  - Campo Saltillo - 1945-1950 Campo San Gaspar - 1945 (Box 70, Folder 786)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Correspondence - Construction, 1952-1953 (Box 70, Folder 787)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Correspondence - General, 1952-1962 (Box 70, Folder 788)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Correspondence - General, 1952-1962 (Box 70, Folder 789)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Listas de Raya, 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 790)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Listas de Raya, 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 791)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Listas de Raya, 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 792)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Listas de Raya, 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 793)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Listas de Raya, 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 794)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Listas de Raya, 1959-1960 (Box 70, Folder 795)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Listas de Raya, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 796)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Reports - Annual, 1954-1955 (Box 71, Folder 797)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Reports - Miscellaneous, 1952-1962 (Box 71, Folder 798)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Reports - Miscellaneous, 1952-1962 (Box 71, Folder 799)
  - Campo Santa Elena - Reports - Miscellaneous, 1952-1962 (Box 71, Folder 800)
  - Campo Tepalcingo, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 801)
  - General Files - Camp Budgets, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 802)
  - General Files - Contracts, 1952-1960 (Box 71, Folder 803)
  - General Files - Correspondence - General, 1953-1960 (Box 71, Folder 804)
  - General Files - Correspondence - I.N.I.A., 1961-1962 (Box 71, Folder 805)
  - General Files - Estructuras S.A., 1952-1956 (Box 71, Folder 806)
  - General Files Meeting of Camp Directors - 1959 Meteorological Data - 1957-1958, 1957-1959 (Box 71, Folder 807)
  - General Files - Reports - Camp Summaries, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 808)
  - General Files - Reports - Camp Summaries, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 809)
  - General Files - Reports - Camp Summaries, 1954-1955 (Box 72, Folder 810)
  - General Files - Reports - Camp Summaries, 1954-1955 (Box 72, Folder 811)
  - General Files - Reports - Miscellaneous, 1951-1960 (Box 72, Folder 812)
  - General Files - Reports - Tractor Tests, 1955-1958 (Box 72, Folder 813)